So now we are going to update the firmware of Proc Spark three device.
So before updating the firmware, make sure you are in the same client directory as before.
So it's proc mark three clients directory.
Let me clear out the screen.
All right.
So the first command to update the prox mark three.
First of all, let me tell you how to update the firmware.
So it's a little tricky.
But at the same time, it's also very easy.
So before updating the firmware or before connecting the device for update for the firmware, make sure
you have press the side button on prox mark three and then you connect the device with your laptop or
your PC, right?
So, uh, the button should be pressed and then the device should be connected.
So when the device will connect, the red and green led will blow up, will light up.
So it will make easier for you to know that the prox mark three is ready for the firmware update.
So make sure the side button is pressed.
And when the device is connected, the green and red led is turned on.
So now we will run our first command to update the firmware.
So it's flasher.
Then we have to give the directory div ty cm0 and then we have to give the boot file.
Bootrom obj.
Bootrom.
Dot elf.
Right.
So let's just hit enter and let's just connect our x mark three.
Make sure the button is pressed and then connect.
So the red and.
Uh, criminality will be.
Blinking.
And let's just wait to update the firmware so it will update the firmware in seconds.
So as you can see, flashing and resetting hardware all done.
Have a nice day.
So that means our first file is updated successfully.
Now we have to update the full image so we will run the flasher again.
So make sure you have disconnected your Proxmox three.
So now we will run our second command for flashing the firmware.
So it's again in the same directory and we will run flasher.
Then we have to give the directory dev t zero.
And then it's in directory src object directory and full image dot.
So let's just run this command.
And again, we have to press the prox, mark three side button and then connect.
So the red and green led will turn on.
And then it will flash.
The firmware.
So make sure you have keep that button pressed until the full image is flashed.
So it's flashed now.
So I'll release the button and all done.
So this is how you update firmware on Proxmox three.
So the firmware is totally updated and let's just clear out the screen.
And let's just run the prox mark three device.
So it's Mach three.
Then we have to give the directory.
So it's connected.
Let's just do hardware tuning.
So it's tune.
The command is tune.
So it will just tune the hardware and it will check all the frequencies.
And it will also display a graph.
So let's just do version as well.
That will show you the version and we can do status as well.
So it will just display the status.
Right.
So these are the basic commands.
In the coming videos, we are going to see how we can use Proc Smart three to find vulnerabilities in
our classic cod.